<?xml version="1.0"?> 
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>

<title>The Stanford Review</title>
<description>The Stanford Review provides weekly political and campus commentary during the school year.  We strive to offer an alternative viewpoint to what is generally expressed at Stanford University.</description>
<link>http://www.stanfordreview.org</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2008 The Stanford Review</copyright>

<item>
<title>ASSU Holds $500k of Student Money in Unspent ‘Reserve’ Fund</title>
<description>An investigation into ASSU finances has revealed a massive reserve fund of over $500,000 in unspent student money. According to data supplied by the Capital Group at Stanford Student Enterprises, which manages the money, the fund has grown over 35% since this year’s graduating seniors entered Stanford as freshmen in 2004.</description>
<author>Tristan Abbey and Quinn Slack</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.stanfordreview.org/Archive/Volume_XL/Issue_9/News/news1.shtml</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Iraq Critics Reject Claim War Was for Oil</title>
<description>In exclusive interviews with the Stanford Review, three of the most prominent critics of the Iraq War—Paul Pillar of Georgetown, Stephen Walt of Harvard, and John Mearsheimer of Chicago—rejected the assertion that acquiring Iraqi oil was America’s motive for invading.</description>
<author>Tristan Abbey</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.stanfordreview.org/Archive/Volume_XL/Issue_9/News/news2.shtml</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Publisher of Muhammad Cartoons Clarifies Free Speech</title>
<description>Of all the incidents involving Islam and free speech in recent years—with the possible exception of the “teddy bear” case in Sudan late last year—the crisis of the now-infamous “Muhammad cartoons” stands out, primarily for the absurdly disproportionate reaction in the Muslim world vis-a-vis what prompted it.</description>
<author>Jonathan Gelbart</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.stanfordreview.org/Archive/Volume_XL/Issue_9/News/news3.shtml</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Sex and the Stanford Bubble</title>
<description>There is a debate on campus over whether birth control pills should be subsidized by the university. Because of the Deficit Reduction Act of 2005, which changed the way that pharmaceutical companies paid rebates to the states, pharmaceutical companies can no longer offer birth control pills to college health care clinics at discounted rates.</description>
<author>Allysia Finley</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.stanfordreview.org/Archive/Volume_XL/Issue_9/News/news4.shtml</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>CCR Brings Film, Videoconferencing to Stanford Students</title>
<description>On May 13th, Stanford students in Wallenberg Theater watched in awe as a team of American students discussed the Iraq war with a team students in Baghdad. Bridge to Baghdad, a two-part documentary depicted videoconferences between students in New York and students in Baghdad a few months before, and three years into, the Iraq war.</description>
<author>Allison Rhines</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.stanfordreview.org/Archive/Volume_XL/Issue_9/News/news5.shtml</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Heart of the Matter: Stem Cell Research</title>
<description>This is a question that has been addressed by major philosophers and theologians over the centuries, with answers ranging from conception to time points during development to birth. Personally, my belief is that human life is a continuum.</description>
<author>Tristan Abbey</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.stanfordreview.org/Archive/Volume_XL/Issue_9/Features/features1.shtml</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Interview: The Two Stevens</title>
<description>Steven Pressfield is the bestselling author of Gates of Fire, hailed by critics as an “epic of man and war.” He is a prolific author, having published eight books including the just-released Killing Rommel, set not in ancient times but in the deserts of North Africa, and is also a veteran of the Marine Corps.</description>
<author>Tristan Abbey</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.stanfordreview.org/Archive/Volume_XL/Issue_9/Features/features2.shtml</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Gay Marriage Ruling Raises Constitutional Questions</title>
<description>In 2000, Californians voted on Proposition 22, which sought to define marriage as between a man and a woman. The measure was passed, with 61.4 percent in favor.</description>
<author>Chris Seck</author>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.stanfordreview.org/Archive/Volume_XL/Issue_9/Opinions/opinions1.shtml</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
</item>

</channel>

</rss>				  
			    